the 2020s could be an apocalyptic decade
for wall street as artificial
intelligence takes over the most popular
jobs in finance
when thinking about the future jobs
landscape in the financial industry and
the role of machine learning will there
be jobs gone or job displacement
advance in automation and artificial
intelligence could make 32 of the jobs
in the financial and insurance sector
obsolete
understanding machine learning and data
science will be key for any future job
in the financial sector
in either case whether you think there
will be jobs gone or job displacement
machine learning is going to change the
financial ecosystem and job landscape
for decades to come it's extremely
important to realign and at least
understand the key role and function
that automation and machine learning
will play within the financial industry
into the future by developing your skill
set in machine learning and ai you can
reinvent yourself to keep up with both
the current and the future jobs
landscape
features of this course include complete
and comprehensive deep dive into almost
every application of finance from
algorithmic trading portfolio management
fraud detection and many more
applications
it's open source programming packages
and tools available in python
it's practical application with over 15
case studies using real-world data
and most importantly it's affordable
most similar courses are one thousand
dollars plus and aren't even as
comprehensive or practical as this
this course offers a complete practical
and affordable way to gain insights into
the relevant ways that machine learning
is improving the financial industry